<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Recipal</string>
    <string name="title_activity_ingredient_search">IngredientSearch</string>

    <string name="recipe1">Chicken Noodle Soup</string>
    <string name="recipe2">Lentil Soup</string>
    <string name="recipe3">Hot Artichoke Dip</string>
    <string name="recipe4">Guacamole</string>
    <string name="recipe5">Crispy Edamame</string>
    <string name="recipe6">Grilled Chicken with Lemon</string>
    <string name="recipe7">Spinach Enchiladas</string>
    <string name="recipe8">Vegetable Lasagna</string>
    <string name="recipe9">Penne Pasta Salad</string>
    <string name="recipe10">Red Lentil Curry</string>
    <string name="recipe11">Lemon Bars</string>
    <string name="recipe12">Strawberry Shortcake</string>
    <string name="recipe13">Chocolate Cupcakes</string>
    <string name="recipe14">no</string>

    <string name="description1">Chicken Noodle Soup is a trcfraditional soup using boiled chicken, pasta,
    carrots, peas and light herbs</string>
    <string name="description2">Lentil Soup is made from a mixture of various lentils soaked in water
    overnight and boiled</string>
    <string name="description3">Hot Artichoke Dip is a dip made using Spinach, Artichokes and cream.
    It is best eaten with chips</string>
    <string name="description4">Guacamole is a traditional mexican dish made using Avocados, Tomatoes,
    Onions, Cilantro, and Lime. It is best eaten with chips but can also be eaten alongside various
    dishes</string>
    <string name="description5">Crispy Edamame is a traditional Japanese Dish made using Edamame beans
    and is eaten as an appetizer</string>
    <string name="description6">Grilled Chicken with Lemon is a entre made to taste using various herbs.
    It\'s strongest flavor is lime</string>
    <string name="description7">If you like spinach and Mexican food, you\'ll love this dish.</string>
    <string name="description8">Vegetable Lasagna is a pasta dish made with pasta layered on top of each
    other with marinara sauce and various ingredients in between</string>
    <string name="description9">Penne Pasta Salad is a cold pasta dish made using various beans, penne pasta,
     and pesto sauce</string>
    <string name="description10">Red Lentil Curry is a rich and hearty dish. Great as a main dish, but can
    also be eaten as a side dish. This dish is amazing with Basmati Rice</string>
    <string name="description11">An intensly flavored layer of lemon custard, on top of a crisp, sweet shortbread
     crust makes these cookies almost like little slices of lemon pie.</string>
    <string name="description12">Old fashioned Strawberry Shortcake dessert has tender homemade shortcake
     layered with sweet strawberries and fresh whipped cream</string>
    <string name="description13">Ready in 30 minutes, this quick dessert is great for parties.</string>

    <string name="ingredient1">1 tablespoon butter, 1/2 cup diced carrot, 1/2 cup diced onion, 1/2 cup
    diced celery, 1 pinch salt, 1/4 teaspoon thyme leaves, 2 tablespoons melted chicken fat, 2 quarts
    roasted chicken broth, 4 ounces uncooked noodles, 1 pinch cayenne pepper, 1 pinch salt and ground
    pepper</string>
    <string name="ingredient2">1 chopped onion, 1/4 cup olive oil, 2 diced carrots, 2 stlks of celery
    chopped, 2 minced cloves of garlic, 1 teaspoon of dried oregano, 1 bay leaf, 1 teaspoon of dried
    basil, 1 can crushed tomatoes, 2 cups dry lentils, 8 cups water, 1/2 cup sliced spinach, 2
    tablespoons vinegar, salt, ground pepper</string>
    <string name="ingredient3">1 can artichoke hearts, 1/3 cup grated Romano cheese, 1/4 cup grated
    Parmesan cheese, 1/2 teaspoon minced garlic, 10 ounces of chopped spinach, 1/3 cup heavy cream,
    1/2 cup sour cream, 1 cup shredded mozarella</string>
    <string name="ingredient4">3 avocados peeled and mashed, 1 lime juiced, 1 teaspoon salt, 1/2 cup
    diced onion, 3 tablespoons chopped fresh cilantro, 2 roma tomatoes diced, 1 pinch ground cayenne
    pepper</string>
    <string name="ingredient5">12 ounces shelled edamame, 1 tablespoon olive oil, 1/4 cup grated
    Parmesan cheese, salt and pepper</string>
    <string name="ingredient6">1 3/4 cups Chicken Stock, 3 tablespoons lemon juice, 1 teaspoon dried
    basil leaves, 1 teaspoon dried crushed thyme, 1/8 teaspoon ground pepper, 4 chicken breast halves
     skin removed</string>
    <string name="ingredient7">1 tablespoon butter, 1/2 cup sliced onions, 2 minced cloves of garlic,
     10 ounces of chopped spinach, 1 cup ricotta cheese, 1/2 cup sour cream, 2 cups shredded monterey
     jack cheese, 10 corn tortillas, 1 can enchilada sauce</string>
    <string name="ingredient8">16 ounces lasagna noodles, 3/4 cup chopped green peppers, 3/4 chopped
        onion, 3 minced garlic cloves, 2 tablespoons vegetable oil, 2 jars pasta sauce, 1 tablespoon
    dried basil, 1 container ricotta cheese, 4 cups shredded mozarella cheese, 2 eggs, 1/2 cups grated
    parmesan cheese</string>
    <string name="ingredient9">1 package dry penne pasta, 2 peeled and cubed cucumbers, 2 diced roma tomatoes,
    2 cups loose corn, 1 can kidney beans, 2 tablespoons lemon juice, pepper, 1 cup cilantro, 1 cup
    sliced celery</string>
    <string name="ingredient10">2 cups red lentils, 1 large onion diced, 1 tablespoon vegetable oil,
    2 tablespoons curry paste, 1 tablespoon curry powder, 1 teaspoon ground turmeric, 1 teaspoon ground
     cumin, 1 teaspoon chili powder, 1 teaspoon salt, 1 teaspoon white sugar, 1 teaspoon minced garlic,
    1 teaspoon minced fresh ginger, 1 can tomato puree</string>
    <string name="ingredient11">2 1/4 cup all purpose flour, 1/2 cup confectioners\' sugar, 1 cup
    softened butter, 4 eggs, 1 1/2 cups white sugar, 1/2 cup lemon juice, 1 tablespoon lemon zest</string>
    <string name="ingredient12">1 quart fresh sliced strawberries, 1/4 cup white sugar, prepared sponge
     cake dessert cups, 1 can whip cream</string>
    <string name="ingredient13">1 1/3 cups all purpose flour, 1/4 teaspoon baking soda, 2 teaspoons
    baking powder, 3/4 cup unsweetened cocoa powder, 1/8 teaspoon salt, 3 tablespoons softened butter,
        1/12 cups white sugar, 2 eggs, 3/4 teaspoon vanilla extract, 1 cup milk</string>
    


    <string name="instruction1">Melt butter in a large soup pot over medium heat. Stir in carrot,
        onion, celery, salt, and fresh thyme. Stir in chicken fat; cook and stir until the onions
        turn soft and translucent, 5 to 6 minutes. Stir in roasted chicken broth and bring to a boil.
     Season to taste with salt, if necessary; stir in noodles and cook until tender, about 5 minutes.
     Stir in cooked chicken breast meat and simmer until heated through, about 5 minutes. Season with
        cayenne pepper, salt and black pepper to taste.</string>
    <string name="instruction2">In a large soup pot, heat oil over medium heat. Add onions, carrots,
        and celery; cook and stir until onion is tender. Stir in garlic, bay leaf, oregano, and
        basil; cook for 2 minutes. Stir in lentils, and add water and tomatoes. Bring to a boil.
        Reduce heat, and simmer for at least 1 hour. When ready to serve stir in spinach, and cook
        until it wilts. Stir in vinegar, and season to taste with salt and pepper, and more vinegar
        if desired.</string>
    <string name="instruction3">Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C). Grease a 9x13 inch
        baking dish. In a blender or food processor, place artichoke hearts, Romano cheese, Parmesan
        cheese and garlic . Pulse until chopped, but not ground. Set aside. In a medium bowl, mix
        together spinach, heavy cream, sour cream and mozzarella cheese. Stir in artichoke mixture.
        Spoon into prepared baking dish. Bake in the preheated oven for 20 to 25 minutes, or until
        cheese is melted and bubbly.</string>
    <string name="instruction4">In a medium bowl, mash together the avocados, lime juice, and salt.
        Mix in onion, cilantro, tomatoes, and garlic. Stir in cayenne pepper. Refrigerate 1 hour for
        best flavor, or serve immediately.</string>
    <string name="instruction5">Preheat the oven to 400 degrees F (200 degrees C). Place the edamame
        into a colander and rinse under cold water to thaw. Drain. Spread the edamame beans into the
        bottom of a 9x13 inch baking dish. Drizzle with olive oil. Sprinkle cheese over the top and
        season with salt and pepper. Bake in the preheated oven until the cheese is crispy and
        golden, about 15 minutes.</string>
    <string name="instruction6">Stir the stock, lemon juice, basil, thyme and black pepper in a
        small bowl. Lightly oil the grill rack and heat the grill to medium. Grill the chicken for
        35 minutes or until it\'s cooked through, turning the chicken over halfway through cooking
        and brushing often with the stock mixture. Discard the remaining stock mixture.</string>
    <string name="instruction7">Preheat the oven to 375 degrees F (190 degrees C). Melt butter in a
        saucepan over medium heat. Add garlic and onion; cook for a few minutes until fragrant, but
        not brown. Stir in spinach, and cook for about 5 more minutes. Remove from the heat, and mix
        in ricotta cheese, sour cream, and 1 cup of Monterey Jack cheese. In a skillet over medium
        heat, warm tortillas one at a time until flexible, about 15 seconds. Spoon about 1/4 cup of
        the spinach mixture onto the center of each tortilla. Roll up, and place seam side down in a
        9x13 inch baking dish. Pour enchilada sauce over the top, and sprinkle with the remaining
        cup of Monterey Jack. Bake for 15 to 20 minutes in the preheated oven, until sauce is bubbling
        and cheese is lightly browned at the edges.</string>
    <string name="instruction8">Cook the lasagna noodles in a large pot of boiling water for 10
        minutes, or until al dente. Rinse with cold water, and drain. In a large saucepan, cook and
        stir mushrooms, green peppers, onion, and garlic in oil. Stir in pasta sauce and basil;
        bring to a boil. Reduce heat, and simmer 15 minutes. Mix together ricotta, 2 cups mozzarella
        cheese, and eggs. Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C). Spread 1 cup tomato sauce
        into the bottom of a greased 9x13 inch baking dish. Layer 1/2 each, lasagna noodles, ricotta
        mix, sauce, and Parmesan cheese. Repeat layering, and top with remaining 2 cups mozzarella
        cheese. Bake, uncovered, for 40 minutes. Let stand 15 minutes before serving.</string>
    <string name="instruction9">Bring a large pot of lightly salted water to a boil. Add penne
        pasta and cook for 8 to 10 minutes or until al dente; drain. Combine pasta, corn, tomatoes,
    celery, kidney beans, corn, lemon juice and pepper. </string>
    <string name="instruction10">Wash the lentils in cold water until the water runs clear. Put
        lentils in a pot with enough water to cover; bring to a boil, place a cover on the pot,
        reduce heat to medium-low, and simmer, adding water during cooking as needed to keep covered,
        until tender, 15 to 20 minutes. Drain. Heat vegetable oil in a large skillet over medium heat;
        cook and stir onions in hot oil until caramelized, about 20 minutes. Mix curry paste, curry
        powder, turmeric, cumin, chili powder, salt, sugar, garlic, and ginger together in a large
        bowl; stir into the onions. Increase heat to high and cook, stirring constantly, until
        fragrant, 1 to 2 minutes. Stir in the tomato puree, remove from heat and stir into the lentils.</string>
    <string name="instruction11">Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C). Mix 2 cups of flour
        and confectioner\'s sugar together. Cut in the butter or margarine. Mix well until the dough
        resembles pie dough consistency. Press the dough into a 9x13 inch baking pan. Bake 15 to 20
        minutes or until golden brown. Beat together eggs, sugar, 4 tablespoons flour, lemon juice
        and lemon rind for at least 1 minute. Pour the mixture over the baked crust. Bake the bars
        another 20 minutes, or until the lemon topping has set. Sprinkle with confectioner\'s sugar
        when cooled. </string>
    <string name="instruction12">Place strawberries in a container with a lid; add sugar and stir to
        coat. Place lid on the container and refrigerate until sugar has dissolved, at least 15
        minutes. Place a 1 dessert cup in each serving bowl and put as many strawberries as you like.
        Top each with whipped cream.</string>
    <string name="instruction13">Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C). Line a muffin pan
        with paper or foil liners. Sift together the flour, baking powder, baking soda, cocoa and
        salt. Set aside. In a large bowl, cream together the butter and sugar until light and fluffy.
        Add the eggs one at a time, beating well with each addition, then stir in the vanilla.
        Add the flour mixture alternately with the milk; beat well. Fill the muffin cups 3/4 full.
        Bake for 15 to 17 minutes in the preheated oven, or until a toothpick inserted into the cake
        comes out clean. Frost with your favorite frosting when cool.</string>


    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="emptyString" />
    <string name="empty2" />
    <string name="empty3" />
    <string name="empty4" />

    <string-array name="Recipe1">
        <item>Cucumber-Carrot Salad</item>
        <item>vinegar</item>
        <item>sugar</item>
        <item>oil</item>
        <item>ginger</item>
        <item>salt</item>
        <item>carrot</item>
        <item>onion</item>
        <item>bellpepper</item>
        <item>cucumber</item>
        <item>Whisk rice vinegar, sugar, vegetable oil, ginger, and salt together in a bowl until sugar and salt are dissolved into a smooth dressing. Toss carrot, green onion, bell pepper, and cucumber in the dressing to evenly coat. Cover bowl with plastic wrap and refrigerate until chilled, about 30 minutes.
    </item>


    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Recipe2">
        <item>Insalata Caprese with Avocado</item>
        <item>avocados</item>
        <item>lemon</item>
        <item>tomatoes</item>
        <item>basil</item>
        <item>salt</item>
        <item>oil</item>
        <item>mozzarella</item>
        <item>Combine avocados and lemon juice in a large bowl; toss to coat. Add tomato, mozzarella, and basil; toss again. Drizzle with olive oil and season with salt
</item>


    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Recipe3">
        <item>Light Lemon Pesto Pasta</item>
        <item>spaghetti</item>
        <item>cheese</item>
        <item>garlic</item>
        <item>spinach</item>
        <item>basil</item>
        <item>walnuts</item>
        <item>lemon</item>
        <item>salt</item>
        <item>oil</item>

        <item>Bring a large pot of lightly salted water to a boil. Cook spaghetti at a boil until cooked through but firm to the bite, about 12 minutes; drain. Transfer spaghetti to a large bowl. Put cubed Romano cheese in the bowl of a food processor; process until coarsely grated, about 30 seconds. Put garlic into the food processor and process until the cheese and garlic are combined. Add spinach, basil, walnuts, lemon juice, lemon zest, and salt; process until the mixture comes together into a thick paste. Scrape down the sides of the bowl with a spatula. With food processor running, drizzle olive oil into the mixture. Continue processing until the oil is integrated smoothly. Pour sauce over spaghetti and toss to coat
    </item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Recipe4">
        <item>Mozzarella and Tomato Appetizer</item>
        <item>tomatoes</item>
        <item>prosciutto</item>
        <item>mozzarella</item>
        <item>basil</item>
        <item>dressing</item>
        <item>Thread each toothpick with: one tomato, 1/4 of a slice of prosciutto folded into a small square, one mozzarella ball, one basil leaf (folded if it is large), and one more tomato. Arrange appetizers on a serving platter. Drizzle with your favorite Italian salad dressing.
</item>


    </string-array>


    <string-array name="Recipe5">
        <item>Pasta with Pesto and Scallops</item>
        <item>fettuccine</item>
        <item>pesto</item>
        <item>oil</item>
        <item>onion</item>
        <item>garlic</item>
        <item>wine</item>
        <item>mushroom</item>
        <item>bellpepper</item>
        <item>In a large pot with boiling salted water cook fettuccini pasta until al dente. Drain. Stir in pesto sauce and 2 tablespoons of olive oil. Meanwhile, in a large skillet, saute onion and garlic in 3 tablespoons olive oil until soft. Add green bell pepper, mushrooms and cook until soft, about 3 minutes. Stir in dry white wine, lemon juice, salt and pepper to taste, and bring to a boil. Add scallops and toss for 2 minutes. Take care not to overcook the scallops, as they will toughen when exposed to prolonged heat. Toss the pesto covered pasta with the scallop sauce. Sprinkle with grated Parmesan cheese. Serve immediately.
    </item>


    </string-array>


</resources>
